Guide to the Silicon Valley Ephemera Collection, 1976- M0443
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Publications, Series 1
  - General, Subseries 1.1
    - Sun Microsystems, Inc. Promotional brochures, 1987; 3 items (Box 24, Folder 6)
      Includes product information on Sun's worskstations, information on Sun's open systems networking strategy, as well as Sun's Catalyst program.
    - Sun Microsystems, Inc. Promotional brochures, 1994; 3 items (Box 24, Folder 7)
      Includes brochure on Java computing, a letter from David Schwartz regarding Inquiry, and an informational brochure on publishing solutions using Sun's workstations.
    - Sun Microsystems, Inc. Sunrise professor architecture, Ver. 6, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Sun Microsystems. SunWorld conference materials, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Sunshine Power Company. Product information, 1977; 1 item (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Sybex. Introduction to Word Star / Arthur Naiman. -- 2nd ed. -- Berkeley: Sybex, 1982; 1 item (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Symantec Corporation. Promotional brochures and journals, 1989-1995; 9 items (Box 25, Folder 2)
      Transfer, 199
      Promotional brochures for Norton Utilities and Disc Doctor; THE NORTON NEWSLETTER, Winter 1989; promotional trading cards; SYMANTEC, Autumn 1990.
    - Symmetric Computer Systems. Price list, 1986 Aug 25; 1 item. (Box 25, Folder 3)
      Symmetric Computer Systems
    - Synergistic Designs. Directory of biotechnology firms, 1994; 1 item. (Box 25, Folder 4)
      BIOTECH BAY, directory of biotechnology firms in the Bay Area, including an illustrative map of the area with company locations.
    - Synkareon Computer Services. The 'Word-processor's Krutch', undated; 2 items (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Syntex Corp. Informational brochure, 1987; 1 item (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Systems Services Specialists. Class announcement, undated; 1 item (Box 25, Folder 7)
      Systems Services Specialists.
    - T/Maker Company. Product catalogue, 1986; 1 item. (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Tandem Computers. Company literature, 1995; 3 items. (Box 25, Folder 9)
      Company literature on multimedia and digital media network components.
    - Target Technology. Artificial Intelligence Business Newsletter, 1985; 3 items (Box 25, Folder 10)
      Journal entitled Artificial Intelligence Business Newsletter, v. 1, issue 7, September 1985, flyer promoting the journal and an article entitled IBM Boosts AI Industry.
    - Tech Museum of Innovation. Dreams Realized: invitation, 1995; 2 items. (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Tech Museum of Innovation. Flyers, promotional material, etc., 1998 - 2000; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Technology Center of Silicon Valley journal, 1989 - 1990; 2 items (Box 25, Folder 13)
      copy of UPDATE, 1989 Spring, 1990 Spring.
    - Teknowledge, Inc. Annual report, Sep-86; 1 v. (Box 25, Folder 14)
      Teknowledge, Inc.; Hecht, Lee
    - TeleAdapt, Inc. Promotional brochures for international modem adapters, 1997; 6 items. (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Telecommunications Reports, Inc. Electronic Mail & Messaging Systems (EMMS), 1996; 1 v. (Box 25, Folder 17)
      Journal entitled EMMS ELECTRONIC MAIL & MESSAGING SYSTEMS, EXCLUSIVE BIWEEKLY INTELLIGENCE ON TECHNOLOGY, APPLICATIONS, PRODUCTS & MARKET TRENDS, v. 20, n. 21, October 28, 1996.
    - TeleVideo. Price lists, circa 1986; 3 items. (Box 25, Folder 18)
      TeleVideo
    - Terminal 19/84, 1983 July (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - TPS Electronics. Product announcement, 1986; 2 items. (Box 25, Folder 20)
      TPS Electronics.
    - Tri-tek, Inc. Product information, undated; 1 item (Box 25, Folder 21)
      Tri-tek, Inc.
    - Tug lines, Issue no. 7, Vol. 1, no. 3 - 6, 1984-1986, undated (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - TurboPower Software. Informational brochure, undated (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Tymeshare, Inc. Papers [1 of 3], 1968-1979 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Tymeshare, Inc. Papers [2 of 3], 1968-1979 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Tymeshare, Inc Papers [3 of 3], 1968-1979 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Ukiah Software, Inc. Promotional pamphlets for NetRoad FireWALL, 1996-1997; 4 items. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - United States. Executive Office of the President. Office of Science and Technology Policy. A research and development strategy for high performance computing, 1987 Nov 20; 1 item. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - United Transformer Corp. product brochures, 1963 - 1964; 1 v. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Univation. Product announcements, 1986; 5 items (Box 26, Folder 5)
      Univation
    - University of California Extension. Eighth annual institute in Computer Science: program announcement, undated; 1 item (Box 26, Folder 6)
      University of California Extension.
    - Upside Publishing Company. Upside, 1994; 3 v. (Box 26, Folder 7)
      UPSIDE: THE BUSINESS MAGAZINE FOR THE TECHNOLOGY ELITE, May 1994, June 1994, October 1994.
    - /usr/group, 1981 - 1983; 10 items (Box 26, Folder 8)
      Includes newsletter
    - USWeb Corporation. Promotional pamphlet, 1997; 1 item. (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Varian Associates. Annual reports, 1986 - 1987; 2 items. (Box 26, Folder 10)
      Simpson, Gary E.
    - Varian Associates. Company literature, 1987-1993; 10 items. (Box 26, Folder 11)
      Includes prospectus for employee stock purchase, 1987 10-K annual report, promotional pamphlets, company literature and cover letter for 1993 material.
    - Varian Associates. Product brochures [1 of 2], 1987-1993 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Varian Associates. Product brochures [2 of 2], 1987-1993 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Varian Associates: an early history (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Varian Instrument Applications, Vol. 18, no. 2; Vol. 19, no. 1, 1989 - 1990; 2 items. (Box 26, Folder 15)
      Varian Associates
    - Varian magazine, Vol. 31, no. 1; Vol. 32 [i.e. 31], no. 4; Vol. 32, no. 4 -5; Vol. 33, no. 3-5, 1986 - 1988; 3 items. (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - West Coast Computer Faire Preview, 1 item (Box 27)
    - VDOnet Corp. Promotional brochures and article reprint from a journal entitled INTERNET WORLD, 1996-1997; 8 items. (Box 27, Folder 1)
      Promotional materials for video on demand, and a press release from INTERNET WORLD magazine, November, 1996.
    - Ven-Tel Inc. Product announcement, circa 1986-1987; 1 item. (Box 27, Folder 2)
      Ven-Tel Inc.
    - Venture Electronics. Product description, undated; 1 item (Box 27, Folder 3)
      Venture Electronics.
    - Verbatim Corporation. Papers [1 of 3], 1977-1980 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      Gift of Reid Anderson, 1987
      Verbatim Corporation
    - Verbatim Corporation. Papers [2 of 3], 1981-1987, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Verbatim Corporation. Papers [3 of 3], undated; 3 photographs: col. + 1 photograph: bw (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Verity, Inc. Promotional materials, article reprint from a journal entitled DATABASE PROGRAMMING & DESIGN, and a copy of a journal entitled SEARCH & DEPLOY, 1996; 12 items. (Box 27, Folder 7)
      Promotional materials, article reprint from DATABASE PROGRAMMING & DESIGN, December 1996 Special Issue, v. 9 no. 13, and copy of a journal entitled SEARCH & DEPLOY, v. 5, n. 13, December 16, 1996.
    - Versatec. Promotional flyer, 1986; 3 items. (Box 27, Folder 8)
      Versatec; Xerox Corporation
    - Vidar Corporation. Product catalogs, capability reports and annual reports, 1966-1972; 10 items (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Video Terminology Technology, Inc. Product announcement, undated; 1 item (Box 27, Folder 10)
      Video Terminology Technology, Inc.
    - VisComm, 1994; 1 item (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Visionics Corporation. Price list, 1986; 1 item. (Box 27, Folder 12)
      Visionics Corporation
    - Voyager. Product catalogs, 1994; 4 items. (Box 27, Folder 13)
      Catalog of CD-ROMS entitled 3SIXTY, Fall 1994 and Winter 1994 issues. Also an interim catalog entitled 1EIGHTY.
    - VR & VR World conferences, 1994 - 1995; 2 items (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - VXtreme, Inc. Promotional pamphlet for Web Theater 2, 1997; 1 item. (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Web Innovation, 1997; 1 item (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - WebTV Networks, Inc. Promotional brochure for Web TV, circa 1995; 1 item (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Western Institute in Computer Science. Promotional brochure for Institute held at Stanford University, Department of Computer Science, 1989; 1 item (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Weitek Corporation. Promotional flyers, circa 1987; 2 items. (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Whistle Communications Corp., 1997; 2 items (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Whittaker Xyplex, 1996; 2 items (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Windows NT Intranet solutions conference, 1997; 4 items (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Windows & OS/2 Conference materials, 1992; 2 items (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Wintergreen Research, Inc. Report regarding the internet, 1996; 1 item (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Wired magazine: promotional material, circa 1995; 5 items (Box 28, Folder 1)
      Subscription information and literature on WIRED magazine.
    - WITI (Women in Technology International) annual conference, 1997; 1 item (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Wolfram Research, Inc. plastic bag, 1 item (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Women's Action Alliance. Do your female students say "No, thanks" to the computer?, 1987; 1 item (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - WordStar International Inc. Promotional pamphlet, circa 1985; 1 item (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - WordTech Systems, Inc. Product announcement, 1987; 1 item (Box 28, Folder 6)
      WordTech Systems, Inc
    - World Congress on Expert Systems, 1994 Jan (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Wyse Technology. Product announcements, 1986; 14 items (Box 28, Folder 8)
      Wyse Technology
    - Xaos Tools, Inc. Promotional postcard, ca, 1993; 1 item (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Xerox Corporation. Papers, 1986; 6 items (Box 28, Folder 10)
      Product announcements and advertising. Includes John H. Dessauer's book, MY YEARS WITH XEROX, Palo Alto (Calif.): PARC; 1986.
      Xerox Corporation.
    - Xerox PARC (Palo Alto Research Center). Digests of recent research: cognitive sciences and cognitive technologies, mid-1981 - mid-1983, 1 v. (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Xerox PARC (Palo Alto Research Center). Digests of recent research: intelligent systems laboratory, mid-1983 - mid-1986, 1 v. (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Xerox PARC (Palo Alto Research Center). The optical mouse and an architectural methodology for smart digital sensors / by Richard F. Lyon, 1981; 1 v. (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Xerox PARC (Palo Alto Research Center). Teaching Smalltalk / by Adele Goldberg and Alan Kay, 1977 (Box Series 1 Half box 1)
      Shoup, Richard
    - Xerox PARC (Palo Alto Research Center). Personal Dynamic Media / by the Learning Research Group, 1975 (Box Series 1 Half box 1)
    - Xerox PARC (Palo Alto Research Center). Smalltalk-72 Instruction Manual / Adele Goldberg and Alan Kay, Editors, 1976 (Box Series 1 Half box 1)
    - Xerox PARC (Palo Alto Research Center). A Smalltalk Photo Album (Box Series 1 Half box 1)
    - Xerox PARC (Palo Alto Research Center) Learning Research Group. "Personal Dynamic Media", 1975 (Box Series 1 Half box 1)
    - Xerox PARC (Palo Alto Research Center). Toolbox Illustrator Studes / by William Bowman and Robert Flegal, 1976 (Box Series 1 Half box 1)
    - XeroxWorld, 1998 Winter; 1 item (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Xyram Corporation. Investment prospectus, 1984; 1 item. (Box 28, Folder 15)
      Pamphlet entitled THE MARKETING OF XARS: AN INVESTMENT PROSPECTUS.
    - Ylem. Newsletter, 1981; 1 item (Box 28, Folder 16)
      Ylem (Organization)
    - Z Enterprises. Silicon Valley napkin, 1986; 1 item. (Box 28, Folder 17)
      Z Enterprises
    - Zon Technologies, undated; 1 item. (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Z-World. Promotional flyer, circa 1986; 1 item. (Box 28, Folder 19)
      Z-World
    - Microsoft Corporation. Promotional flyer & journal, circa 1987-2000; 3 items. (Box 31)
      Brochure for Microsoft Excel for the Macintosh plus two copies ONE-TO-ONE WITH MICROSOFT
    - Computer Currents, 1985; Seven issues of COMPUTER CURRENTS, 2nd year, no. 3, 4, 16; 3rd year, no. 8, 13, 14, 16, (Flat-box 29)
    - Macintosh Today, 1988; Six issues of MACINTOSH TODAY, Vo. 2, no. 5-6, 10-11, 14-15 (Flat-box 29)
    - Diskette Gazette. -- International Datawares Inc., Issue no. 4, 5, 6, 11, circa 1986-1988; Two issues of DISKETTE GAZETTE, issue no. 5, 6 (Flat-box 29)
      International Datawares Inc.
    - Intelligent machines journal (Flat-box 29)
    - Microsoft Corp. From our perspective, anything's possible: broadside, undated Jan 12 (Flat-box 30)
    - MPD: Microwave Product Digest, 1992 - 1993; Ten issues of MPD, 1992 Apr., May, June, July/Aug., Sept., Oct. (2 copies); 1993 Jan., Apr., June (Flat-box 30)
    - Microtimes: Northern California's computer magazine, 1985 - 1995; Five issues of Microtimes, Vol. 2, no. 11 (2 issues); no. 34, no. 37; 136 (Flat-box 30)
    - Random Access: newsletter, 1986-1987; 5 items (Flat-box 31)
    - RAG: Random Access Guide, 1983 - 1987 (Flat-box 31)
    - San Francisco Examiner: Seybold Special, 1993 (Flat-box 31)
    - Online design, 1993 Oct; 1 issue. (Flat-box 31)
    - Santa Clara County (Calif.). Planning Dept.: General Plan. Santa Clara County., 1 item (Flat-box 31)
    - Wescon. Daily News, 1987., 1 item (Flat-box 32)
    - Silicon Gulch Gazette, Vol. 0, no. 0-3; Vol. 2, no. 1-4; Vol. 3, no. 1; Vol. 6, no. 1W - 2W; Vol. 7, no. 1; no. 29; no. 34; no. [35?]; no. 41-42, 1977 - 1985 (Flat-box 32)
    - Amen International, Inc. The original Silicon Valley map & [1995] calendar, 1994; 1 item: 24 x 38 in. (Box 1)
      Purchased, 1995.
      Shows company logos and locations of businesses on a pictorial map of Silicon Valley.
    - San Jose: map. -- In San Jose Mercury News, 1986; 1 item (Box 1)
    - Asset Management Company. West Coast Venture Capital -- 25 years, 1958-1983: poster, 1984; 1 item, 39"x45" (Map-tube 1)
      Gift of Asset Management Company, 1984.
      Over 300 people in over 100 companies have built west coast venture capital in these 25 years; most are shown on this chart. Lists individuals and companies with dates of activities and name changes. Researched and edited by Cathie Johnson.
      Venture capital -- California; Johnson, Cathie
  - Alpha Industries, Subseries 1.2
    - Alpha Industries. Semiconductor Division. Specifications, application notes, packages, 1985; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 33, Folder 1)
      Gift of L. Libby
  - Avantek, Subseries 1.3
    - Avantek. DR2A-T1 microwave digital radio primer, 1973; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Beckman Instruments, Inc., Subseries 1.4
    - Beckman Instruments, Inc. Informational pamphlet, 1994; 2 items. (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Informational pamphlet on the Beckman Heritage Center, Fullerton, California with explanatory letter.
    - Beckman Instruments, Inc. Cermet trimming potentiometers technical bulletin, 1974 Apr; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Cisco Systems, Inc., Subseries 1.5
    - Cisco Systems, Inc. Annual Report and promotional flyer, 1995-1997; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Annual report, 1995, including CD-ROM, and promotional flyer for a seminar.
    - Cisco Systems, Inc. Annual Report, 1998; 1 item. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Cisco Systems, Inc. Annual Report, 2000; 1 item. (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Communications Transistor Corp., Subseries 1.6
    - Communications Transistor Corp. Solid circuits: reliability, 1973 Mar; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Communications Transistor Corp. Solid circuits: circuit techniques, 1973 Mar; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Daico Industries, Inc., Subseries 1.7
    - Daico Industries, Inc. Engineering handbook & reference drawings: IF/RF components, 1984; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Dalmo Victor, Subseries 1.8
    - Dalmo Victor. Dalmo Victor system spectrum, [1960-]; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Dalmo Victor. Dalmo Antennas and antenna systems, [1960-]; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Eitel-McCullough, Inc., Subseries 1.9
    - Eitel-McCullough, Inc. EIMAC quick reference catalog, 1961; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - ELCA Battery Co., Subseries 1.9
    - ELCA Battery Co. Product brochures, circa 1973; Accession no. 2003-322 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Fairchild Semiconductor Corp., Subseries 1.10
    - Fairchild Semiconductor. Catalog, 1973 Feb; 1 v. (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Fairchild Camera and Instrument Corp. Diode data book. -- Mountain View: Fairchild, 1978; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 32, Volume 1)
    - Fairchild Microwave and Optoelectronics. Catalog and price list, 1970; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Fairchild Camera and Instrument Corp. Voltage regulator handbook. -- Mountain View: Fairchild, 1978; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 32, Volume 2)
    - Fairchild Semiconductor. Product information, 1968; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Fairchild Semiconductor. Microwave transistors, 1969; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Intel Corp., Subseries 1.11
    - Intel Corporation. Promotional pamphlets, flyers, catalogs, 20-year retrospective, 1988-1997; 7 items. (Box 10, Folder 10)
      Includes 20 year history, museum visitor's guide,
      Intel Corporation; Wyle laboratories
    - Intel Corporation. Product announcements & museum guide, 1983-1987; 2 items. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Intel Corporation. Promotional pamphlets, flyers, catalogs and disc, company 20- and 25-year retrospectives, retrospective of Robert Noyce, newspaper clippings, and annual report [1 of 4], 1994, 1983-2001 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      Noyce, Robert N. (Robert Norton)
    - Intel Corporation. Promotional pamphlets, flyers, catalogs and disc, company 20- and 25-year retrospectives, retrospective of Robert Noyce, newspaper clippings, and annual report [2 of 4], 1994, 1983-2001 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Intel Corporation. Promotional pamphlets, flyers, catalogs and disc, company 20- and 25-year retrospectives, retrospective of Robert Noyce, newspaper clippings, and annual report [3 of 4], 1994, 1983-2001 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Intel Corporation. Promotional pamphlets, flyers, catalogs and disc, company 20- and 25-year retrospectives, retrospective of Robert Noyce, newspaper clippings, and annual report [4 of 4], 1994, 1983-2001 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Intel Corporation. Annual report, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Intel Corporation. Annual report, 1997 - 1998 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Intel Corporation. Annual report, 1999 - 2000 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Intel Corporation. Museum poster, 1990; 1 item. (Flat-box 29)
      Intel Corporation
    - Intel Corporation. Company 25-year retrospectives, 1993 (Flat-box 29)
  - Lockheed Missles & Space Co., Subseries 1.12
    - Lockheed Corporation. Catalog, circa 1968; 1 item (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Lockheed Corporation. Lockheed Horizons, 1986; 1 item (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Lockheed Corporation. Journal, 1992 June; 1 item (Box 11, Folder 33)
      LOCKHEED TODAY journal, June 1992.
    - Lockheed Corporation. Annual report: technology for the eighties, 1979; 1 item (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Lockheed Missiles and Space Company. The Lockheed Star: 25th anniversary newsletter, 1979 May 11; 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Gift of Jean Rice, 1986
      Lockheed Missiles and Space Company.; Fuhrman, R.A. Rice, Jean.
    - Lockheed Missles & Space Co. Some notes on the design of microwave stripline components. -- Technical Report: Ground Digital Electronics, 1962 Apr; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Lockheed Missles & Space Co. Some notes on the design of microwave stripline components. -- Technical Report: Communications, 1962 Dec; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Lockheed Missles & Space Co. A method for the numerical solution of a nonlinear differential equation resulting from an extension of Neeteson's equations on ferrite cores. -- Technical Report, 1963 Jan; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Lockheed Missles & Space Co. Articles by Martin Blumberg, undated; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Monolithic Dielectrics, Inc., Subseries 1.13
    - Monolithic Dielectrics. Product brochures, [196-]; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Monolithic Microsystems, Inc., Subseries 1.14
    - Monolithic Microsystems, Inc. Product brochures, 1984; Accession no. 2003-322 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Murata Erie North America, Inc., Subseries 1.15
    - Murata Erie North America, Inc. Catalog, 1985; Accession no. 2003-322 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - National Semiconductor Corp., Subseries 1.16
    - National Semiconductor Corporation. Annual report, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - National Semiconductor Corporation. Annual reports, 1987, 1989; 2 items (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - National Semiconductor Corporation. National anthem, 1987 Winter; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - National Semiconductor Corporation. National gram, Vol. 1, no. 2; Vol. 3, no. 1-2; Vol. 4, no. 1-2, 1988 - 1990 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - National Semiconductor Corporation. Technology in Review, Vol. 1, 1988 Spring; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - National Semiconductor Corporation. Technology in Review, Vol. 7, circa 1990; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 6)
      Copy of journal TECHNOLOGY IN REVIEW, vol. 7, ca. 1990
    - National Semiconductor Corporation. Corporate university relations packet (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - National Semiconductor Corporation. Promotional material (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - NCR Corporation. Promotional pamphlet, 1993; 1 item. [Note: item missing] (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - NEC Corporation. Pamphlet promoting NetMC software, 1997; 1 item. [Note: item missing] (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - NETCOM On-Lin Communications Services, Inc. Promotional flyer, price lists and points of presence directory of phone numbers, 1996-1997; 4 items. (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - netLibrary information packet, undated; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - NetManage, Inc. Promotional pamphlet with cover letter, 1995; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - NeTPower, Inc. Promotional pamphlet, 1993; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 14)
      Promotional pamphlet advertising NeTPower personal computers.
    - Nevada Western. Product announcements, 1987; 5 items (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - New Computer Swapper magazine, 1988 June/July; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - New industry speaks about Santa Clara County, California, circa 196- (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - New Media Expo, 1994 - 1995; 2 items (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - New York Virtual Reality Expo, 1993; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Newman Computer Exchange. Catalog, undated; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 20)
      Newman Computer Exchange.
    - North Star Computers. Papers, 1978-1986; 5 items (Box 17, Folder 21)
      Product catalogs and notes by Gilbert Dean about North Star founders, Chuck Grant and Mark Greenberg
      North Star Computers.
    - Northern California SGML Users Group flyer, 1993; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Novalogic promotional flyer, 2001; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - National Semiconductor Corp. CMOS. -- Santa Clara, Calif.: National Semiconductor, 1978; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 32, Volume 3)
    - National Semiconductor Corp. Discrete databook. -- Santa Clara, Calif.: National Semiconductor, 1978; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 32, Volume 4)
    - National Semiconductor Corp. Linear applications handbook 1. -- Santa Clara, Calif.: National Semiconductor, 1978; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 32, Volume 5)
    - National Semiconductor Corp. Linear applications handbook 2. -- Santa Clara, Calif.: National Semiconductor, 1978; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 32, Volume 6)
    - National Semiconductor Corp. Linear databook. -- Santa Clara, Calif.: National Semiconductor, 1978; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 32, Volume 7)